{
    "id": "a88c46a6727e4ebc8934aebf65edb72a",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Stand, Turn, And Set",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d31aaab7b65e4e40ab3f6b37ba544747",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Turn, Stand, And Set",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The factory turns …………………. hundreds of bicycles every day.",
                    "description": "To turn out is to produce. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I did go to their place but they turned me ………………",
                    "description": "To turn somebody away is to refuse to allow them to enter a place. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "away",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They turned …………………. our offer.",
                    "description": "To turn something down is to reject it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "down",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her arrogance turned me ………………..",
                    "description": "To turn someone off is to make them feel bored or disgusted.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "away",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had invited all of my friends but none of them turned .....................",
                    "description": "To turn up is to put in an appearance.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "in",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He turned ………………. to be a traitor.",
                    "description": "If something turns out, it proves to be the case.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog turned ………………. the visitor without any provocation.",
                    "description": "To turn on is to attack.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "away",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We shall be invincible if we stand ………………… one another.",
                    "description": "To stand by someone is to support them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "by",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must have the courage to stand …………………. for our rights.",
                    "description": "To stand up for something is to act in support of it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The High court set ………………….. the decree of the lower court.",
                    "description": "To set something aside is to annul a legal decision.",
                    "answers": [
                        "aside",
                        "on",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He immediately set ...................... building a business.",
                    "description": "To set about is to start doing something with determination.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "about",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We set ……………….. in the morning.",
                    "description": "To set off is to begin a journey.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "about",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}